// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Profits do not have to be shared. This statement refers to ………?",
    answer: "Sole proprietorship",
    options: [
      "Partnership",
      "Joint Hindu family business",
      "Sole proprietorship",
      "Company"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The maximum number of partners allowed in the banking business is:?",
    answer: "Ten",
    options: [
      "Twenty",
      "Ten",
      "No limit",
      "Two"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The structure in which there is a separation of ownership and management is called",
    answer: "Company",
    options: [
      "Sole proprietorship",
      "Partnership",
      "Company",
      "All business"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The minimum number of partners required to form a partnership business is?",
    answer: "Two",
    options: [
      "Twenty",
      "Ten",
      "No limit",
      "Two"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " partner whose association with the firm is unknown to the general public is called ?",
    answer: "Secret partner",
    options: [
      "Active partner",
      " Sleeping partner",
      "Nominal partner",
      "Secret partner"
    ]
    
  },
  {
 numb: 6,
 question: "The Head of the joint Hindu family business is called",
 answer: "Karta",
 options: [
    "Proprietor",
    "Director",
    "Karta",
    "Manager"
  ]  

  },
  
    {
 numb: 7,
 question: "The Karta in Joint Hindu family business has ",
 answer: "Unlimited liability",
 options: [
    "Limited liability",
    "Unlimited liability",
    "No liability for debts",
    "Joint liability"
  ]  

  },
    {
 numb: 8,
 question: "In a Co-operative society, the principle followed is ",
 answer: "One man one vote",
 options: [
    "Salary or wages",
    "One man one vote",
    "No vote",
    "Multiple votes"
  ]  

  },
      {
 numb: 9,
 question: "The capital of a company is divided into a number of parts each one of which is called …………",
 answer: "Share",
 options: [
    "Profit",
    "Dividend",
    "Interest",
    "Share"
  ]  

  },
      {
 numb: 10,
 question: "The liability of a sole trader is ………",
 answer: "Unlimited",
 options: [
    "Unlimited",
    "limited",
    "No liability",
    "none"
  ]  

  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

   //  {
    // numb: 7,
   //  question: "Your Question is Here",
  //  answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
   //  options: [
   //    "Option 1",
    //   "option 2",
    //  "option 3",
    //   "option 4"
   //  ]
   //},
];
